blastam.com 2017-11-28

# Privacy - Blast Analytics & Marketing

Blast Analytics & Marketing (“Blast”, “us” or “we”) respects the privacy of the visitors to its Website, the home page of which is located at http://www.blastam.com (“Website”) and its App downloadable to your app-enabled mobile device (“App”). This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any Personal Information and Anonymous Information you submit to us through our Website or App. Unless otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms shall have the meanings assigned to such terms set forth in the Blast Terms and Conditions that you can find at [Terms and Conditions](http://www.blastam.com/terms) and which incorporate this Privacy Policy by reference.

“Personal Information” is information about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, address, email address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. “Anonymous Information” means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect and use Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### User Consent

By submitting Personal Information through our Website or App, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy.

Your Personal Information may be processed by Blast in the country where it was collected as well as transferred to and processed in other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

### Collection of Personal Information

The Personal Information we gather from you helps us learn about visitors to the Website or users of the App, our customers and potential customers. We use this information to provide the Services to you, to better tailor the features, performance and support of our products and services, and to offer you additional information and opportunities.

### Personal Information You Provide to Us

We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Website or App.

  * When you register on the Website or App, we may collect your full name and username, a password, and an email address.
  * When you order products or services on the Website or App, we will collect all information necessary to complete the transaction, including your name, credit card information, billing information and shipping information. We do not store credit card information.
  * When you subscribe to a Blast newsletter, we will collect your email address.
  * When you contact us to submit comments, questions or feedback using the forms on the Website or in the App, we will collect your name, email address and your comment, question or feedback.
  * When you participate in one of our surveys, we may collect additional profile information.
  * When you contact us using the request forms on the Website or in the App, we will collect your name, email address and your comment or question that you enter into the form.
  * When you contact us by sending us an email, we will collect your email address and any information contained in the email you send us and any information attached to the email.

### Personal Information Collected Via Technology

As you navigate our Website or App, certain information may also be passively collected, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, domain names, access times, operating system, mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and which you viewed. This type of information is collected to analyze the use of our services and solutions and to make them more useful to you. Like other aspects of our services, we use a third party service provider for some or all of this type of data collection and analysis; these third party service providers may also independently collect information about you as described in “Disclosure of Personal Information” below.

An “Internet protocol address” or “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We track IP Addresses solely in conjunction with session cookies to analyze our web page flow.

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a web site. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Website or App. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Website or App may not work properly.

### Personal Information We Receive From Other Sources

Any information we collect from you via our Website or App will only be used to serve you and improve the products and services we provide.

### Use of Information

In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better. We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with the Blast newsletters, surveys, or promotional emails regarding changes and upgrades to our products and services and for other marketing purposes of Blast, should you request to receive such communications from us.

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you. We may use this Anonymous Information to analyze request patterns and usage patterns so that we may enhance our products and services. Blast reserves the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to third parties in its discretion.

### Feedback

If you provide feedback on any of our products and services to us, we may use such feedback for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. Blast will collect any information contained in such communication and will treat the Personal Information in such communication in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Disclosure of Personal Information

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not trade, rent, or share your Personal Information with third parties and we will not disclose financial information that is part of your Personal Information unless you ask us to do so.

We may share your Personal Information with third parties to provide you with the products and services that we offer you through the Website or App. These third parties are required not to use your Personal Information other than to provide the products and services requested by Blast and are bound by confidentiality agreements with regard to their use of such information. You expressly consent to the sharing of your Personal Information with our contractors and third party service providers for the sole purpose of providing products and services to you.

We may enter into co-branding or co-promotional agreements with third parties pursuant to which we may share Personal Information with such third parties. For example, we may enter into agreements with Partner Companies pursuant to which we provide the Partner Companies with a URL and a customer registration page co-branded with, or private labeled by, the Partner Companies, and the Partner Companies distributes and promotes the URL to its customers. A Partner Company may have access to Personal Information that we collect from their customers. As a result, if you register on the Website or App through a Partner Company, we may provide your Personal Information to the Partner Company. Please note, however, that we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties.

We use third-party advertising and/or web analytics companies to serve ads and/or to provide us web analytics when you visit our Website or App. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites (e.g., through the use of cookies) in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you, to provide us analyses of how our site is used. Although we do not authorize these third parties to collect your Personal Information from our Website or App, they may associate data collected about your use of our Website or App with the personally identifiable information they have collected about you from other websites. If you would like to opt out of third-party advertising behavior collection and use, you may do so at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

We may share some or all of your Personal Information with companies under common control such as any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or parent company (collectively, “Affiliates”), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Information (as described below), we may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on Blast; or (b) to protect and defend the rights or property of Blast or users of our Services.

### Advertising

This site uses Google Analytics data that may be examined in concert with data about our ads that have been shown using the Google Display Network or DoubleClick for Advertisers. Anonymous user information is collected by the use of cookies to help us track user interaction with this website after users see our ads and to enable us to optimize our ad campaigns.

This site also uses Display Advertising via Google Analytics for Remarketing. Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet and use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this website. We use analytics data to also serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this website.

You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising, DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising or customize Google Display Network ads by using the [Ads Preferences Manager.](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCgmN_jHP_vcZaAELuo6xkZDxhnRmjJGcFvaO9jjV6tvVtXRC13n2CToIf6rtSxrlDRJi31Maqt6oNYwOAilJ6jhIxX1vRdrxww5sT_5ajvFHWBhxtCDOGd67lzaxepM6yGlmFbMA2mX2GWeSk1h8CvvC-52uHGrobJgceVYaP0RJtH0BMHWsDn0JfuAq3DFmBiXxj6033ez0jAPOCh-nsdpOF2meiLKdpGDdAB1cmdSVSAk6FiQ0N2B3KW2BsOrNolUSHrn)

### Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, you may request and obtain from us, once a year, free of charge, certain information about the Personal Information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for their marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. This information would include a list of the categories of Personal Information that we shared and the names and mailing addresses of all third parties with which we shared Personal Information in the preceding calendar year. If you would like to make such a request, please submit your request to [General Support](http://www.blastam.com/questions-comments).

### Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use and sharing of your Personal Information. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the communication you receive or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below). Despite your indicated preferences, we may send you communications regarding the services we provide to you, such as transaction reports, notices of new Website or App releases, and notices regarding changes to the Website or App, updates to our Terms of Use, Privacy Policy, or other policies.

You may change any of the Personal Information in your account by editing your online profile or by sending an email to us at the email address set forth below.

### Regarding Children

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13.

### Other Sites

Our provision of a link to any other website or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites.

### Security

Blast is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.

Blast has implemented industry-standard electronic means of protecting your Personal Information. We store Personal Information behind a computer firewall, a barrier designed to prevent outsiders from accessing our servers, and we have implemented technology to detect intrusions. We also require you to enter a password to access your account information. In addition, Blast protects your Personal Information from unauthorized physical access by storing your Personal Information in a controlled facility. Except as provided elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, Blast limits access to Personal Information in electronic databases to those persons (including employees and contractors) in Blast’s organization who have a business need for such access. Lastly, we conduct periodic internal audits and vulnerability scans to ensure compliance with these security measures and generate security incident logs that track Information useful in screening for attempted abuse of or unauthorized access to your Personal Information.

Even though Blast has taken significant steps to ensure that your Personal Information is not intercepted, accessed, used, or disclosed by unauthorized persons, you should know that Blast cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

### Contact Us

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us through [General Support](http://www.blastam.com/questions-comments) or:

Blast Analytics & Marketing  
Attention: Arielle Deakter  
6020 West Oaks Blvd., Suite 260  
Rocklin, CA 95765  
USA

### Privacy Policy Updates

This Privacy Statement is a living document. As part of the Blast Terms and Conditions, this Privacy Policy is subject to occasional amendment, in accordance with the terms of the Terms and Conditions.

This Policy was last updated on October 1, 2015.
